<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Dwayne McDaniel&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>https://dwayne-mcdaniel.com/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Dwayne McDaniel&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 13:45:53 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://dwayne-mcdaniel.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Veterans Day, testing out AgilityCMS and manually deploying my first Netxt.js site anyhow</title>
      <link>https://dwayne-mcdaniel.com/posts/veterans-day-agiltycms-nextjs/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 13:45:53 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dwayne-mcdaniel.com/posts/veterans-day-agiltycms-nextjs/</guid>
      <description>I took most of Veterans Day off. I did not serve in the military myself, instead doing civil service through Americorps, but I am grateful for those who did go off to war and defend the ideals I get to enjoy. I like to review history of service on this day. Learning from history will hopefully help us all avoid mistakes in the future. So I canceled all my meeting and dedicated some time to reflection.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nextjs Conf 2020</title>
      <link>https://dwayne-mcdaniel.com/posts/nextjs-conf-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2020 23:37:30 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dwayne-mcdaniel.com/posts/nextjs-conf-2020/</guid>
      <description>The NextJS Conference 2020: 70K registered and saw so many people on Discord A new blog for a new leg of my journey I am super excited to write my first personal blog post about my experiences at a conference in my new industry: the first ever NextJS Conference! This was by far the largest virtual event I have taken part in and it was super well organized and flowed really well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why I Build Dumb Things</title>
      <link>https://dwayne-mcdaniel.com/posts/why-i-build-dumb-things/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2019 12:22:09 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dwayne-mcdaniel.com/posts/why-i-build-dumb-things/</guid>
      <description>I like building dumb ideas out.
Here are a few of my favorites:
CSSCMS - A static site generator based on stuffing everything we can into CSS.
Clean and Soap Bar - A strange little joke on a website lending legitimacy to a company.
Am I Online Or Not Dot Info - The most primitive example I could build of a microservice.
KevinThull.com - A glorious inside joke in the Drupal community to build a GithubPage Kevin Thull himself can not open pull requests for.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Old Friends Are the Best</title>
      <link>https://dwayne-mcdaniel.com/posts/old-friends-are-the-best/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 08:32:26 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dwayne-mcdaniel.com/posts/old-friends-are-the-best/</guid>
      <description>As I was on my way to PressNomics I was waylaid by the airline industry mismanagement of things and got stranded overnight in Denver. One of the best benefits of being as old as I am though is that I have made a lot of friends and acquaintances over the years pretty much all over the country and certain parts of the world. So, I thought &amp;ldquo;who do I know in Denver who might let me crash with them?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
